uzmarketing.com 2016-04-15

# UZ Marketing Privacy Policy

**Information about Privacy on UZmarketing**

UZmarketing is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement only applies to UZmarketing ; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the complete UZmarketing privacy statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing and/or registering UZmarketing products. Personal information collected by UZmarketing often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. 

For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase in the Shop area of the Web site, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number.

When you buy a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. We keep this registration information on file with any information you’ve already given us on previous visits to our Web site.

UZmarketing also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of UZmarketing.

UZmarketing also collects information about which pages our customers visit within UZmarketing. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique ID number, and it is never linked with personal information.

**Use of your Personal Information**

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To ensure our site is relevant to your needs.
  * To deliver services, such as newsletters, that you request.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from UZmarketing, if you so request.
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate.

We will merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content. In some limited-entry sections of UZmarketing, with your approval, we will combine site-visitation data with your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
